Oita Prefecture on the coast of Kyushu
30 minutes drive from the city of Rep
There is a town where animals live deep in the mountains that can be called cowardly
The name of the place is African Safari
In the vast 1.15 million square meter prairie
The only safari park in Kyushu
The only safari park in Kyushu.
This video is a real document of these animals and these four people.
and these four people.
Gao Ranger at the Tokyo Bay Area
Hi, I'm Shach!
Where are you?
In the mountains of Oita.
It's a very natural path.
It's nice.
You're here?
Certainly.
Let's see what we can find.
What is it? Oh, it's huge! Wow!
Hey, there's a bad one.
That's Max.
I know it's Max. I know it.
We're greeted by a giant statue of an elephant.
Spring is not very fond of kangaroos, so this video is a little bit of a shocker.
The idea of getting a two-shot with a kangaroo and Spring...
I can't even get a two-shot.
It's a secret dream.
That's because I don't go near trees.
But maybe I'll get to see
Maybe we'll get to see some motherhood for the first time.
We've never had any motherhood before.
Oh, yeah.
First motherhood?
First motherhood.
For the first time.
The four of them are enjoying their casual conversation.
But they're about to find out how tough the animal world can be.
the harshness of the animal world.
Arrival
Arrival at Fritter stream
Dazzling
Pony is a general term for horses under 147 centimeters tall
Hello
Hello.
I wonder if he's hungry.
He's got a leaf on his head.
He's cute.
Hello. - Hello.
Why are you so still?
Is it itchy skin?
It's itchy.
Is it tasty?
He's so cute.
He's so cute!
The white one is cute, too.
Hey, big brother!
Big brother!
Chew on that, guys. What are you doing?
Is it good?
Is it itchy?
Familky?
Yuzuki, the carrots are here!
Oh, my God! You sure?
Eat up. I want some.
What? Yum!
It looks just like him!
Yes, they look exactly the same.
Aren't you happy?
Who wants some!
Oh! I ate a familkie!
You want some?
I want some!
Careful with that.
I want a carrot!
Calm down!
You want to try?
I'll try.
Wow!
Why is my hair like that?
What was Sakamoto so surprised about?
This is what it is.
Wow!
Whoa!
No!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Give me a little tease. Give me a little tease.
Wow! I'm out of bullets!Wow! I'm out of hits!
Next pony, next pony.
The pony in the back has pushed the pony in front of him out of the way!
It's a world where the law of the jungle is the law of the jungle!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I wish I had one of those.
Hey, I'm looking at you, I'm looking at you
I'm looking at you and I'm looking at you and I'm looking at you and I'm looking at you.
Hey!
Black toy.
Oh, my gosh.
He's amazing... he's an elder... and he's been here a long time.
Oh, here he comes.
Come here.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God!
At an angle.
Why is it so bad?
There are many ways to find food. And here he comes.
When a senior comes along, he's got to move out of the way.
There's a big seniority system.
So there's a hierarchy in the pony world.
Is it strict? Are you a strict senior?
Oh, my God, your lips are pouting.
Your ass is more like an ass.
Hal, give it up.
Where's the slant-eater? Slant-eater.
The slant-eater went that way.
She went away because you came.
How many did you eat?
Too many! You're too big!
Give it to the little one.
You ate too much! Hurry up!
Go get the little girl over there! The one with the black, round, round eyes.
Oh, look, I want to give it to her!
Frustrated boss pony
That's when it happened.
I'm having so much fun! It's so much fun!
So much fun!
Then, no more ponies.
I'm satisfied with ponies.
It's so much fun!
I've never laughed so much in a zoo.
Little did they know.
They didn't know that this was just the beginning of the book.
The sound of insects...
I can hear the bugs.
Oh, my God!
It moves, like a waterfall.
Hey!
Next...
This is good.
I don't know where we'll end up next.
I don't know, but there are a lot of buildings.
The animals are there at random.
We're walking around with no plan.
Ah! Kangaroos! Kangaroos?
Sakamoto's natural enemy, the kangaroo, is in the corner.
What is Sakamoto so afraid of?
He's getting up!
The kangaroo's appearance is something the four of us never imagined.
I think I know what Haru means.
I know, right guys?
It's a little scary, isn't it?
Yeah, it's a little scary.
Pon-chan seems safe
Wow!
The three of us are looking at each other in a row.
It'll be fun.
I'm gonna go check it out.
How are you?
That's so funny.
I couldn't find the right words to describe it.
I'll see you later. Bye.
Wow, there's a lot of them!
There are so many!
Heh heh heh heh!
Wow, I thought they were kangaroos, but they're all kangaroos!
All of them!
Mmmmmm...
Oh man, it's surreal, isn't it?
What we saw was not the cute kangaroo we are familiar with.
This is a kangaroo!
Is this their true form?
Shall we go then?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
You've got a different emotion than cute again.
I think everyone understands a little better now, don't you? Haruno says...
Well, it's a little bit obvious, isn't it?
It's not just the cute ones, it's the animals you don't expect to see.Seeing animals that are not only cute, but also unexpected.
Little by little
The four girls' emotions seem to be changing.
Delicious. They've decided to take a short break.
Can I take first place so far?
You guys want to go with me?
Uh, what division?
First place in my memory of my memories.
Okay.
Overall.
Here we go.
You're saying it?
One shot.
In one shot.
In my mind.
I'll never forget it.
It can be cute or not.
It could be either.
It could be a healing experience.
It could be an animal that left a lasting impression on me.
Seino.
Oni (ogre).
Definitely the same.
It left a lasting impression on me.
Story-type.
Good night.
After all, everything is an exchange of feelings.
I can't help it, you know?
An exchange of feelings.
I went to see the show like I was being shown it.
I'm grateful for all the feelings I'm getting from you.
I'm just trying to move their feelings.
We're really proud of you.
We were angry.
It seems that the experience was invaluable for the girls.
After a short break, the four of us were ready for the main event!
The jungle bus!
The Jungle Bus is an ecology observation bus that takes you to a vast expanse of grassland to feed the wild animals that are released there.
We are going to the wild wild animals!
Growing anticipation for the wild animals!
But the girls will witness even more of nature's harshness!
Let's go this way.
Oh, here we go!
Yay!
It's a little hairy.
It's hairy.
It's got hair.
I've never seen a sheep so hairless.
What, you think it's a deer?
Not a yahtzee?
The first thing we saw was a sheep.
Sheep are the oldest domesticated animal
The oldest domesticated animal in the history of mankind.
Although we are not accustomed to seeing them, sheep were originally horned creatures.
Because horns are dangerous to humans, they are often cut off when they are domesticated.
Tasty?
Yes?
Is it there?
I think they're cute.
He's cute.
Next, we were greeted by...
The American bison is the largest mammal in North America.
It stands nearly two meters tall, and a large individual can weigh more than 900 kilograms.
The bison is a symbol of the land of the free and is a much-loved animal in the United States.
They are generally docile, but when push comes to shove, they can run at three times the speed of a human, so be careful.
Next was the rhinoceros. The rhinoceros is said to be the most aggressive creature on land, but it is also very fashion-conscious.
When they find a puddle of water, they sometimes cover their entire body with mud to keep their skin in good condition.
And they sharpen their horns like cats sharpen their claws.
It's really cool.
It's cool, you know?
Okay, well, let me out to the elephant.
The girls are excited to see a large animal.
What awaited them next was an even bigger animal.
Elephant!
It's a big elephant!
An elephant!
Elephants are huge creatures, weighing from 3 to 5 tons.
From the moment it is born, it weighs about 100 kilograms.
It takes a lot of physical strength to move such a huge body.
The elephant flower has evolved so that it can catch food without having to move its huge body,
The elephant flower evolved so that it could catch food without having to move its huge body.
The long flowers are for survival.
Elephants, when they are alive,
One of Tom لم,
Oooh!
Oooh.
Wow.
Oooh.Oh!
Great, great, great, great, great! I ate it, I ate it, I ate it!
You ate it?
It flew right out of my mouth!
Oh, my God!
Wow! I ate it!
That's a weird feeling!
There are two!
Bow eyelashes!
Your hair is so thin!
I didn't know you had hair like this.
I didn't know.
I had long hair.
There was a lot of body.
Here's a new one.
It's huge.
He's got a beard, too.
That's true.
That's amazing.
It's like a horse that's been around for a hundred thousand years.
It's decorated with elephants.
The ears are floppy.
I put body cream on it.
It's so dry.
White.
Sorry, it's gone.
I'm sorry.
Dry.
It's really big.
That's amazing. I've never seen anything like it.
It's amazing.
And then...
The creature suddenly appeared.
It's got a great vibe. It's got a great vibe!
What is this creature?
It's a camel that creates a lot of atmosphere.
Yes, a camel.
Camels are sexy!
I mean, look at the mouth on this one.
A camel fiercely seeking food.
Oh, Mr. Okashi won't eat.
Oh, please.
Let's go again.
Thank you.
The four of them drop the food again and again, as if on purpose.
Frustrated camels
But it wasn't just the camels that were frustrated.
Yes, Daikoku complained about the camel training!
Oh my, it's fun!
But I want one!
Wow!
Oh, here it comes, here it comes!
It's gone! Gone!
Gone!
Oh!
Too cute!
Rast! Rast!
Rast!
Oh, no!
At the end, Yuka!
Oh!
Yuka's at the end!
That was fun! It was fun!
It's easy!
Fun! Fun!
The public was concerned, but the joy was great.
I want to go around again!
Hey!
I found myself spontaneously doing an encore.
The camels were so powerful!
Yuzuki is funny because he is so hard on the camels.
He was so hard on the camels.
The animals welcomed us just the way they are.
I was puzzled at times by their unusual appearance.
There were a few moments of bewilderment.
but their faces were filled with a sense of accomplishment.
I'm back!
A sense of accomplishment!
All of the African Safari
I had a great time!
It was so much fun!
The animals were amazing!
Shocking!
The last one at the end was a shock!
It's so easy!
I wondered why birds are so easy.I wondered why the bird was so easy.
That's what I thought at first.
It made sense.
It was entertaining.
You can't experience the power from this distance.
You should all come.
It was so much fun!
I had a great time in Oita!
Bye bye!
Please like, comment and subscribe!
Thank you!
I want to say more again!
See you soon!
That's all for now, orcas!
Bye bye!
And that was the end of the killing once,
But there was one animal I really wanted to see again.
This creature...
I was a little nervous.
Ha-ha-ha!
Which one was it?
Which one?
They're eating each other.
They're eating each other, Dr. Bishop.
That's right.
The last person I wanted to see one more time was a pony.
Which one?
Well, apparently...
It looks like he wants to feed the ponies that were prevented
that the boss pony prevented them from eating.
But the ponies never came.
In this age of cell phones, we are able to see images of strange animals.
Are these images really true?
They do not live in the images.
They have their own rules and pride.
The human ego has no place on an African safari,
It was a place that showed us the animals as they are.
Please subscribe to our channel.